why are you crying there? Yes, I just don’t
из-за чего у вас там слёзы Да просто не
want to remember what happened and what you
хочу вспоминать то что прошла а что вы
went through. Hello
прошли
Hello, I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky. Are you
Хмельницкий Вы
from the Russian Federation? Well, I see Yes,
откуда с Российской Федерации Ну я вижу
I have a flag showing
Да у меня флажок показы это город
what city Moscow is, I understand you have children
какой Москва понял у вас там дети
watching cartoons there
смотрят мультики
Yes,
Да
look, what are you looking for in a
смот А вы что ищете в
roll?
рулет
So there’s
Так делать
nothing to do, what’s the
нечего что е
Crimea?
Крым
By the way, your children are boys or
у Вас кстати дети мальчики или
girls, what’s the difference? Well, just if they’re
девочки какая разница Ну просто если
boys, then you get money from them;
мальчики то вы бабла с них получается
so that somewhere in another country it
армию чтоб где-то в другой стране
comes out and receives
выходит да и получить
compensation. Well, it turns out that your authorities are
компенсацию Ну получается ваши власти
bad
брот ших
suckers in huge quantities. Yes, wait,
лохов огромных количествах Да подождите
wait. Our men are suckers for you, but
подождите Наши мужчины для вас лохи да
ours are not yours for us, your
наши нет ваши для нас
suckers are for us, yours are your suckers
лохи ваши для нас лохи ваши ваши тоже
for us too. Don’t look at our
для нас получается Не смотрите наши на
our territory And this is why they are persecuting you. So
нашей территории А вас гонят вот ради
tell me if your child grows up.
чего Вот скажите если Вот вырастет ваш
Yes, and he will be thrown into another country
ребёночек Да и его кинут в другую страну
to fight for this. This is why
воевать ради чего вот ради чего сейчас
your guys in
сдохнут Ваши ребята в
Ukraine will
Украине смысл Какой
die now. What is the purpose of the guys now?
цель в основном ребята сейчас идут
sent
контрактники которых туда отправили
correctly Well, here they are for the Motherland, look
правильно Ну вот и за Родину смотри
why, that's why they were sent, that's the
зачем вот зачем их отправили вот какая
purpose I can't [ __ ] I don't want to quarrel with you
цель я не могу сри Я не хочу с вами
I just don't understand why they keep
ссориться Я просто не понимаю почему они
going, going and dying,
всё идут идут и умирают умирают
dying, contract soldiers died, they took their mobile phones, Looks like
контрактники погибли взяли мобили Зро у
someone is on your side too  Yes, yes, in war,
вас походу кто-то тоже есть да на войне
since you
раз вы
look like that with a languid look Yes,
так смотрите с томным взглядом Да вот
this is your husband or brother Who is he if he
этот ваш муж или брат Кто он если он
flies to him something for which he will die
прилетит ему что-то за что он погибнет
for what for
за что ради
what for the sake of
чего ради пацанов
his boys, the majority of us, we sent
своих большинство У нас у нас пошли
most of the guys for the fact that
большинство ребят за то то что там
their friends died there and so it goes and in
погибли их друзья и так оно идёт и
a chain. That is, I understand correctly
цепочкой То есть я правильно понимаю
Putin abandoned their friends, they were killed in
Путин кинул ихних друзей их убили в
Ukraine and the boys are so damn Putin abandoned
Украине и пацаны такие блин Путин кинул
our friends, they were killed, they are not asking a
наших друзей их убили они не ти задают
question, they went so that they could be
вопрос они пошли Чтобы ещё их
killed again No, you didn’t understand me, but
убили Нет вы меня не поняли а как
look, when did this start
смотрите когда это началась вообще
initially, the situation in Ukraine, it
изначально ситуация на Украине же она
started initially in what year, from the
началась изначально с какого года с
fourteenth year, an educated person
четырнадцатого года образованный человек
no, wait, you’re an educated person, it’s
нет подождите вы же образованный человек
clear that you’re older than me and in terms of that,
видно то что старши меня и в плане того
let me ask you when it
давайте я Вас спрошу когда у вас
started for you in general, inside Ukraine,
началась вообще внутри Украины
it turns out inside  countries have
получается внутри страны
their own
своя
war, there was no war, we had, look,
война не было войны у нас было смотрите
we had in 2014, on the night of
у нас было в 2014 году в ночь с 26 на 27
February 26-27, the occupation of Crimea began, then on
февраля началась оккупация Крыма потом с
April 12 of that year, the occupation of the
12 апреля чего года началась оккупация
Donetsk and Lugansk
Донецкой и Луганской
regions began, occupation Yes, the occupation works out for me,
области оккупация Да оккупация у меня
look, I lived in Surgut
получается смотрите я жила в Сургуте у
I had a classmate, she is a migrant from
меня была одноклассница она мигрант
Ukraine, and she herself personally told me
Украины и она сама лично рассказывала
that Lord Bandera, well, roughly speaking, the
что Господа Бандеры вот ну грубо говоря
neighbors shot her, that’s normal.
соседи расстреливали это нормально
Lord Bandera shot her,
Господа Бандеры расстреливали она до сих
she is still undergoing a psychologist to
пор она до сих пор проходит психолога до
this day. I communicate with her, but this is how
сих пор Я с ней общаюсь а вот как как
she saw these  Lord Bandera, where in
она вот видела эти Господа Бандеры где в
what city did she live so that Lord
каком она городе жила чтобы Господа
Bandera would shoot her neighbors about this, you
Бандеры у неё расстреляли соседей о это
need to ask her about this, but this is the
е у неё надо спрашивать но это вот
border,
граница
I don’t remember what this
получается я не помню уже како это
village is like, she lived in a farmstead, the border of what and
посёлок она в хуторе жила граница чего и
what Well, this is not closer to Russia, you know
чего Ну это не ближе к России понимаете
?  so if the border is what is this
А так если граница к чему это это
Donetsk somewhere in the Donetsk region
Донецке где-то в Донецкой области
you know So where where in Donetsk I don’t
понимаете Так а где где в Донецке я не
remember, you know because look
помню вот понимаете потому что смотрите
Donetsk was under the control of Russian troops
Донецк был под контролем российских войс
as if when we met her And
как бы когда мы с ней познакомились И
she told me Well, from me  from memory
она мне сказала Ну у меня из из памяти
stop stop stop you were 16 years old
выле стоп стоп стоп вам было 16 лет
When you met now
Когда вы познакомились сейчас вам
how old are you? Well I’m
сколько ну
years old now I
года
understand and my husband is already there yes yes
понял и муж уже там
he’s been there he’s been there or now he’s
да да он побывал там побывал или сейчас
been there I understand What happened Well you
там побывал понял А что случилось Ну вы
can do that Yes no he came back in one piece  Well, yes,
может Да нет он целый пришёл назад Ну да
of course, he was a contract soldier or whoever
прил конечно он был контрактник или кто
he
он
was, keep equal training is not smo What do you
был держать равно трени не смо У вас что
look at, I started Yes there, there in the words of the
смотри я начинал Да там вот там словами
SDO, let me understand that this is personal for you,
СДО давайте я понял что это у вас личное
it
оно где-то
hurts somewhere, what hurts in your soul, tell
болит что у вас болит на душе скажите
me
мне
of course  Is he now where he is with
конечно Он сейчас где находится он с
you in the city or
вами в городе или
not yes yes yes I think he is Well, why are
нет да да да помоему находится Ну а
you crying there Well, I just
из-за чего у вас там ну слёзы Да просто
don’t want to remember what happened and what
не хочу вспоминать то что прошла а что
you
вы
went through I thought they were just
прошли я я так думал что их просто
being sent to war Well  And everything
отправляют Ну на войну А и всё
[music] is
[музыка]
calm
спокойно
No, not everything is
Нет не всё
calm, not everything is
спокойно не всё
calm And what’s
спокойно А что
not calm? Let’s continue
неспокойно Давайте продолжим дальше
the dialogue about he was in
диалог про он был в
captivity no no no no he wasn’t in
плену нет нет нет нет не был в
captivity I heard he said something there
плену я так слы он там что-то е говорит
Yes, he was nearby he
Да он рядом он
was nearby  in p was in
рядом был в п был в
pst I'm serious, not me I asked I don't
пст я вы серьёзно не я Я спросил Я не
know No, I'll just tell you honestly no no no
знаю Нет просто я вам скажу честно нет
And you
нет не А ты
fought So I understood for sure And that you're not fighting now that they
воевал Так точно понял А что сейчас не
let you go I mean, they
отпустили В смысле что меня
let me go if you're Contra and they're
отпустили если ты Контра ж мобили
taking the mobiles of those called  why didn’t they
званных берут что ж тебя не
take you, maybe constructive, here’s about the con,
взяли можно конструктива вот про кон
look constructive, are you now a
смотри конструктива ты сейчас
military serviceman or
военнослужащий или
not, what is your purpose initially,
нет вы с какой целью вот изначально
just initially Look, I
просто изначально Смотри Я я после
just came in after work after work, here I am, I
работы зашёл просто по у меня вот я до
work until 8:00 pm and then I keep
8:00 вечера работаю так потом все
talking to people Yes  So I want to
разговариваю с людьми Да вот и я хочу
understand, I don’t quarrel with the Russians Yes,
понять вот я не ссорюсь с россиянами Да
I just want to understand, for example, not so
я хочу понять просто например не так
precisely. That’s what’s in her soul.
точно Вот что у неё на душе
I just can’t understand
такое Я просто не могу понять
why the
почему
children were killed. You why which
детей-то детей-то убили Вы почему каких
children were killed? And now you know the question
детей убили А вопрос сейчас вот знаешь
which des I'll love the same
какие дес полюбому такой же
question the same question will be in any way
вопрос такой же вопрос будет по-любому
yes
да
Oh, I now understand that the girl was crying
О я теперь понял что девушка плакала
Let's So you went to
Давайте Так вы ушли на
war in a normal psychological
войну в нормальном психологическом
state, Timur returned in an abnormal state
состоянии вернулись Тимур в ненормально
this Stupid stupid You can do it through
этот Глупый глупый Ты можешь через
a psychologist honestly man
психолога честно мужчина
why why
делать почему почему
then why then  Ukraine is here,
тогда почему тогда Украины есть вот вот
tell it like a man to a man, a man to a man,
скажи как мужчина мужику мужик мужику
say let's
скажи
say it like it is, let's
давайте давай скажи как есть давай
hear
слышишь
the question Why why then why children are
вопро Почему почему тогда почему дети
to blame What children Here you are Yes,
винова Какие дети Вот вы
I'm a
Да я
mortar, look you who you were I
миномёт смотри ты ты кем был я 120
put the 120 mortar then
миномёт ставил тогда
behind in front of the bakhmut That is, look you
за перед бахмутом Вот то есть смотри ты
that is, you came in Bakhmut, people lived,
то есть ты пришёл в бахмуте жили люди
children lived. You came, destroyed, killed. Yes,
жили дети Ты пришёл уничтожили убил Да
you killed the blood on your hands and
ты убил кровь на твоих руках да
absolutely everything, and that’s why your wife is crying
абсолютно всё и поэтому твоя жена плачет
because she understands that the curse is on
потому что она понимает что проклятие на
you and your family now. Because you
тебе и твоём роде теперь Потому что ты
killed people, you destroyed the city with  its
убивал людей ты уничтожил город с его
inhabitants were people, Jews, and Russia, and
жителями люди жили люди жи да Россия и
you specifically are not just Russia, but
Ты конкретно не просто Россия А
specifically
конкретно
you, at the age of 25, killed people,
ты ты в свои 25 лет убивал людей мирных
civilians. You came to their
людей Ты пришёл в ихнюю
country, they lived
страну они жили
peacefully, and you
спокойно жили А ты их
killed them. I just talked to a man,
убивал Я только что разговаривал человек
I just talked to a man.  He is
я только что с человеком разговаривал Он
with Ukraine, believe me, he has more honor than
с Украиной поверь у него больше чест чем
you, it doesn’t matter who you were talking to.
у тебя всё равно с кем ты разговаривал
You tell me who was the grenade launcher who was the
Ты скажи ты кем был гранатомёт ком там
tanker who was the pilot who A And who Yes Who
танкистом кем лётчиком кем А А кем Да
I was yes Who I was you shouldn’t see That is,
Кем был я да Кем был тебя не долж видишь
you even if you  You did your
То есть тебе даже если б ты делал свой с
military duty with honor, you would say I was
честью воинский долг ты бы говорил Я был
this and that and you are ashamed because
тем-то тем-то а тебе Стыдно потому что
you killed people, you killed hundreds and
ты убивал людей ты убивал мирных сотни и
thousands of civilians, it’s on your conscience Yes,
тысячи мирных это на твоей совести Да
they come to you in a dream, they come to
они приходят к тебе во сне приходят
torment
мучают
you And how do you wake up
тебя А как ты просыпаешься
at night Timur the
ночью Тимур
voices don’t
хорошо голоса не
call well Can I ask my wife a question I’m
зовут Можно яй жене вопрос Вот мне
interested I think what you’ll come up with Let me say Well, of course I
интересно Мне кажется что ты придумаешь
don’t understand you’re
Дай вот Ну давай конечно не я понимаю ты
from Ukraine You’re asking questions like that on purpose you
с Украин Ты специально так вопросы
see You see Look at you at
задаёшь видиш Видишь Смотри ты в своих
25 years old instead of taking care
25 лет да вместо того чтобы заниматься
of your family Yes  be near your children
своей семьёй Да быть возле своих детей
Yes, you went to kill other people's children in a foreign
Да ты полез убивать чужих детей в чужую
country to kill you went to kill killed Yes and you
страну убивать пошл убивать убил Да и ты
killed them how many died as a result of children Yes you killed
их убил сколько погибло в результате
children you killed children you
детей Да убил дете ты убил детей ты ть
you killed at least one child you killed at
ты убил детей хоть одного ты убил детей
least one child you killed children you
хоть одного ребёнка ты убил детей ты
killed the children of Mariupol, look at the dead
убил детей Мариуполь посмотри погибший
Bakhmut, take the list of lists, all the children are in
бахмут возьми список списки все дети на
your hands, you were part of and in Bakhmut you
твоих руках ты был в соста и в бахмут
were part of the occupation army, you
был в составе оккупационной армии ты
killed people,
убивал людей с чего ты взял
why did you get it? Why did you take everything
чтоби С чего ты взял все
to those Ukraine, you said that you were there
на теи Украины ты сказал что ты там был
?  crossed the border of Ukraine with
Каждый кто переступил границу Украины с
a weapon, he is a murderer, he is a murderer of our children,
оружием он убийца он убийца наших детей
our people, and your wife, you know why, you
наших людей и твоя жена знаешь почему
know why your wife is crying
знаешь почему твоя жена плачет потому
because she understands that you are a murderer, she
что она понимает что ты убийца она
understands it in her eyes,
понимает это в её глазах читалось вот
give me the camera, let her say that you are not a
дай камеру пусть она скажет что ты не
murderer, let her tell me  she will say to your face that
убийца пусть она мне в лицо скажет что
you are not a murderer, you are afraid to give up the camera, you
ты не убийца ты боишься отдать камеру
see, you won’t give it away, because you know
видишь ты не отдашь Потому что ты знаешь
that she will cry and say that you are a
что она расплачется и скажет что Ты
murderer, it hurts her, she understands that you
убийца это ей болит она понимает что ты
killed other people, tell me to my face,
убивал других людей Скажи мне в глаза
take the camera from her and tell me that
это возьми у неё камеру и скажи мне это
in my
в
eyes I'm the
глаза я
same she she won't say in my eyes Because
те она она не скажет в глаза Потому что
you are a killer You are a killer and she confirms
ты убийца Ты убийца и она подтверждает
she confirms that you are a killer you are at
она подтверждает что ты убийца ты в свои
25 years old Yes you already have blood on your hands Yes and
25 лет Да уже имеешь кровь на руках Да и
your your your wife is crying she looks
твоя твоя твоя жена плачет она смотре
she looked into my eyes  and she cried, she
она с смотрела мне в глаза и ревела она
cried tears, she can’t say And
ревела слёзы она не может сказать А
now I understand why she cried
теперь я понимаю почему она пла Потому
Because I don’t know how you went there but
что я не знаю каким ты ушёл туда но
how you came It’s just tough and She
каким ты пришёл Это просто жесть и Ей
has to live with it She has to
приходится с этим жить Ей приходится
live with this man who has
жить вот с этим человеком у которого
blood on his hands  up to the elbows or
кровь на руках по локоть или по
shoulders next time say you kill me I'll
плечи в следующий раз говори ты убий я
tell you You're a murderer and I tell you more ska
тебе скажу Ты убийца и я тебе больше ска
you beat her in the field
ты её бьёшь полю
Ser Master of Sports in Tas Boxing or something
сер мастер спорта по тас бокс гоните что
You drive your
ли Ты
wife oh let her tell me to my face that you
жену о пусть она мне в лицо скаже что ты
don't
её не
beat her those here  SJ
бьёшь те вот СЖ
lower beats you and you consider him a
пониж ж тебя бьёт и ты считаешь его
murderer yes yes And that’s why you will never
убийцей да да И поэтому ты мне в
say no to my face for anything that’s
глаза-то ни за что не скажешь нет ни за
why he doesn’t give you
поэтому он тебе не даёт специально
a camera on purpose And you don’t take it away from him to
камеру А ты не забираешь у него чтобы
say no to my face Yes you can
сказать мне в глаза нет Да ты можешь
just from afar to say no and no Because
только издалека сказать нет и нет Потому
you're all
что ты всё
gone, here's a degrod and people like that came to
ушло вот дегрод да такие по приходили на
our Earth, subscribe to us Telegram right
нашу Землю подпишись на ми Telegram прям
now Ovin and
зараз овин а
popk more and more respectfully YouTube taking
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg ODS in your ban and I
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
don’t show too many videos to people  We don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about the stream at all times. To that end,
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we need to write a Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away, but while there, in Telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video, there is also Tsikava and Korisna
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we will show you the Trima postiyny
информация и мы пон вами трима постийний
operational link.
оперативный звязок